https://www.perfectionlearning.com/privacy-policy

Series
ACT/SATAlgebra 1 End-of-CourseAMSCO® MathAP® English (AMSCO®)AP® Math (AMSCO®)AP® Social Studies (AMSCO®)Basic Drama ProjectsBenson HandwritingConnections: English Language ArtsConnections: LiteratureConnections: Writing & LanguageCover-to-Cover Hi-Lo BooksEarth Science: The Physical SettingEnglish Language Arts CompanionFirst Person PhysicsFrench Is FunFrench Years 1-4Grammar in PracticeGuided Reading ProgramLiterature & ThoughtMarine ScienceMastering Competitive DebateMath CompanionParallel TextPassages NovelsPerfection ClassicsPerfection Classics—LeveledPerfection Learning® SpellingProjects in Professional CommunicationsProjects in Speech CommunicationReading Essentials® in ScienceReading Essentials® in Social StudiesRetold Tales® LiteratureSpanish Is FunSpanish Years 1-4Vocabulary for the College Bound StudentVocabulary for the High School StudentVocabu-Lit®—Grades 2-5Vocabu-Lit®—Grades 6-12Writing with Power
Subject
Advanced PlacementDrama, Speech & DebateElementary
Language ArtsElementary
LiteracyMathematicsScienceSecondary Language ArtsSecondary LiteratureSecondary ReadingSocial StudiesTest PreparationWorld Languages
Grade
Pre-KindergartenKindergartenGrade 1Grade 2Grade 3Grade 4Grade 5Grade 6Grade 7Grade 8Grade 9Grade 10Grade 11Grade 12
State
IndianaFloridaNew York CitySouth CarolinaTexasVirginia
Book Sets
Advanced Search
Categories
Search
Search
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Information Collected
Perfection Learning® collects anonymous data from visitors to our website in order to make enhancements and improve the quality of your experience. The information collected consists of your IP address (to determine if you are using our website from a school or home), the type of computer you are using (such as a Macintosh or a PC), and the name of the website that referred you to our website.
None of this data can be connected back to an individual user, it is only used for statistical traffic analysis.
We also collect personal information when you buy online from Perfection Learning®. This data includes your name, address, telephone number, and email address. This information would also be needed if you ordered products from Perfection Learning® via the telephone or mail.
Use of Cookies
A cookie is a small bit of information stored on your computer by a website. Perfection Learning® uses cookies to store your shopping cart settings, measure traffic, and determine popular sections of our website. If you have already purchased products online from Perfection Learning, you are given the option to save your name and password for future purchases. This will eliminate the need for you to remember another password.
All of our website is usable without cookies, except for our online shopping cart.
Use of Collected Information
Perfection Learning® uses personal data collected from our website for the purpose of sending you your order and fulfilling product sample and catalog requests. We will also use your email address to send you information on our products and services.
Further Questions
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contactPrivacy CoordinatorPerfection Learning Corporation2680 Berkshire ParkwayClive, IA 50325webmaster@perfectionlearning.com
Continue
View Cart
Compare Products
My Wishlist
